(Leonard:)...standing before a pool of melted snowmen.
There are carrots and coal in the water.
Do we know what happened to the top hats
and the corncob pipes?
- You see those too.
- Oh, it's like I'm really there.
(Stuart:)I gotta tell you,
this is the most holiday fun I've had...
(Stuart:)...since my therapist
changed my anxiety medication...
(Stuart:)...and I stopped caring about the blood
in my stool.
(Howard:)Good story.
- What're you drinking there? Little eggnog?
- Yes. Is there a problem?
(Leonard:)No, it's nice to see you enjoying
a holiday beverage. Pretty Christmasy.
(Sheldon:)Since when is eggnog a Christmas drink?
Eggs are available all year round.
I've been known to enjoy this poolside.
(Leonard:)Come on, Sheldon.
You know all the Christmas stories...
(Leonard:)...and the carols, you've got
an eggnog mustache going on there.
(Leonard:)Just admit it,
you're getting a little yuletide spirit.
(Sheldon:)Don't be silly. Christmas is a bunch of
baloney created by the tinsel industry.